

Prateek Singh Arora

Profile

I am a third year student at Simon Fraser University, majoring in **B.Sc. Computing Science.** I am from New Delhi, India and I am 22 years old.

I am a **punctual** and **professional** individual, currently seeking a **part time/full time** job opportunity for exposure whilst looking to build a **good work ethic** via a proper schedule that includes academics, health and work.

Employment History

Starbucks Barista, Compass Group Canada at SFU, Burnaby

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

Skilled Barista at licensed Starbucks (Compass Group Canada) at SFU. Self taught latter artist, entrusted by managers like a shift supervisor.

IELTS Test Invigilator, IDP IELTS Canada, Vancouver

JULY 2022 - MAY 2023

Engaged as IELTS Invigilator at IDP. Proficiently managed diverse candidate interactions, test logistics and overall support. In-depth test insight from my mother, an IELTS trainer certified by the British Council.

Fashion Sales Associate, Jack & Jones, Vancouver

MAY 2022 - JULY 2022

Fashion sales associate at Jack & Jones, creating rapid customer connections. Learned teamwork and customer preferences. Value fairness and positive environment.

Mover, DLO Move Support Services LTD., Vancouver

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2020

Professional mover at DLO Mover Support. Team-based corporate office relocation specialist. Optimized efficiency, managed sensitive items (including various consulates).

Technology Sales Associate, Staples Canada, INC., Burnaby

NOVEMBER 2019 — JANUARY 2020

Seasonal tech sales associate at Staples Canada. Multifaceted role: customer support, cashier, warehouse, stocking. Valuable customer interactions and diverse experience gained.

Education

Intermediate/Higher Secondary Certificate, ITL Public School, New Delhi

MARCH 2015 - MAY 2019

Volunteer Experience

Peer Education Manager, Fraser International College at SFU

MAY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

Peer Educator, Fraser International College at SFU

JANUARY 2021 - APRIL 2022

Details

3018 St George Street, Unit 204
Port Moody, V3H0L4
Canada
(604) 999-0885
prateek2151@gmail.com

Skills

Computer Skills

Customer Service

Ability to Multitask

Communication Skills

Git

C++

Python

Languages

English

Hindi

Punjabi

Availability

Mon, Wed-Fri: 2 pm onwards
Tuesday: 2:30 pm onwards

Sat & Sun : All day